# Harry Zhe Su

## **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Harry Zhe Su 3710 S. McClintock Avenue, RTH 417, Los Angeles, CA 90089-2905 Email: zhesu@usc.edu Cell: 240-993-9886

Website: https://harryzhesu.github.io/

#### RESEARCH INTEREST

My research interests lie in integrating sensory signals to different levels of planning and control for autonomous manipulation tasks by leveraging machine learning techniques. I investigated tactile servoing where robots directly adapt actions at the rate of perception while gaining better perceptual information. I also worked on learning reactive policies using deep learning techniques, which map erroneous sensory inputs and corrective actions to cope with unconstructed environment. More recently, I have been investigating learning predictive models which update feedforward models based on current sensory inputs. I have evaluated these work on a bimanual manipulation platforms equipped with various sensors. In addition to software development, I also lead in maintaining, debugging, fixing, and upgrading the electrical and mechanical aspects of the robot platform.

## **EDUCATION**

01.2011-Present	Ph.D. in Biomedical Engineering, <b>University of Southern California</b> , Los Angeles, USA Computation Learning and Motor Control Lab, Adviser: Prof. Stefan Schaal
08.2008-05.2011	M.S. in Biomedical Engineering, <b>University of Southern California</b> , Los Angeles, USA Medical Device Development Facility Lab, Adviser: Prof. Gerald E. Loeb
09.2003-07.2008	B. S. in Biomedical/Electrical Engineering, <b>Shenyang University of Technology</b> , Shenyang, China Medical Image Processing Lab, Adviser: Prof. Li Ke

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

01.2015-Present

 $Robotics\ Researcher,\ \textbf{Autonomous}\ \textbf{Manipulation}\ \textbf{Department},$ 

Max Planck Institute for Intelligent Systems, Tuebingen, Germany Research Assistant, Computational Learning and Motor Control Lab,

University of Southern California, Los Angeles, USA

• Developed a hierarchical manipulation framework for autonomous manipulation, which integrates sensory feedback at different levels of planning and control inside perception-action loops.

09.2009-12.2014

Research Assistant, Medical Device Development Facility.

University of Southern California, Los Angeles, USA

- Developed a haptic-enabled robotics system with state-of-the-art manipulators and sensors.
- Developed perceptual models and control algorithms for this system to characterize system properties and various material properties of external objects, such as contact forces, shapes, and compliance.

01.2007-06.2008

Undergraduate Researcher, Medical Image Processing Lab,

Shenyang University of Technology, Shenyang, China

- Developed a EEG classification method for a Brain Computer Interface system using Principal Component Analysis and Nearest Neighbor Classifier.
- Developed a noise reduction method for optical coherence tomography images and coauthored a
  journal paper.

#### **TEACHING EXPERIENCE**

- 08.2012 12.2017 Teaching Assistant, Department of Biomedical Engineering, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, USA BME 620 Applied Electrophysiology,
- 01.2012 05.2018 Teaching Assistant, Department of Computer Science, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, USA CSCI 545 Introduction to Robotics

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

- **Z.** Su, O. Kroemer, G. E. Loeb, G. S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, Learning Manipulation Graphs from Demonstrations Using Multimodal Sensory Signals, in *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2018.
- G. Sutanto, Z. Su, S. Schaal, and F. Meier, Learning Sensor Feedback Models from Demonstrations via Phase-Modulated Neural Networks, in *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2018.
- **Z.** Su, S. Schaal, and G. E. Loeb, Surface Tilt Perception with a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor, in *IEEE International Conference on Biomedical Robotics and Biomechatronics*, 2016.
- Y. Chebotar, K. Hausman, Z. Su, G.S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, Self-supervised Regrasping Using Spatio-temporal Tactile Features and Reinforcement Learning, in *IEEE International Conference on Intelligent Robots and Systems (IROS)*, 2016.
- A. Molchanov, O. Kroemer, **Z. Su**, and G. S. Sukhatme, **Contact Localization on Grasped Objects Using Tactile Sensing**, in *IEEE International Conference on Intelligent Robots and Systems (IROS)*, 2016.
- **Z.** Su, O. Kroemer, G. E. Loeb, G. S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, Learning to Switch Between Sensorimotor Primitives Using Multimodal Haptic Signals, in *International Conference Simulation of Adaptive Behavior (SAB)*, 2016.
- Z. Su, K. Hausman, Y. Chebotar, A. Molchanov, G. E. Loeb, G. S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, Force Estimation and Slip Detection/Classification for Grip Control Using a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor, in *IEEE International Conference on Humanoid Robotics (Humanoids)*, 2015.
- **Z.** Su, J. A. Fishel, T. Yamamoto and G. E. Loeb, Use of Tactile Feedback to Control Exploratory Movements to Characterize Object Compliance, in *Frontiers in Neurorobotics*, 2012.
- **Z.** Su, Y. Li and G.E. Loeb, Estimation of Curvature Feature Using a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor, in 35th Annual Meeting of the American Society of Biomechanics, 2011.
- N. Wettels, J.A. Fishel, **Z. Su**, C.H. Lin, G.E. Loeb, **Multi-modal Synergistic Tactile Sensing**, in *IEEE International Conference on Humanoid Robotics (Humanoids)*, 2009.
- L. Ke, Q. Du, Z. Su, An OCT Image De-noising Method Based on Multi-scale Wiener Filtering, in *Optics and Precision Engineering*, 2008.
- L. Ke, Q. Du, **Z. Su**. The Correlation between the Wavelet Base Properties and Image Compression, in *International Conference on Computational Intelligence and Security*, 2007.

#### REVIEWED WORKSHOP PAPERS AND ABSTRACTS

- **Z.** Su, O. Kroemer, G.E. Loeb, G. S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, Learning to Switch between Sensorimotor Primitives using Multimodal Haptic Signals, in *Robotics Science and Systems (RSS) Workshop on Bootstrapping Manipulation Skills*, 2016.
- A. Molchanov, O. Kroemer, **Z. Su**, and G.S. Sukhatme, **Model-free Contact Localization for Manipulated Objects using Biomimetic Tactile Sensors**, in *IEEE International Conference on Humanoid Robotics (Humanoids) Workshop on Tactile sensing for manipulation: new progress and challenges*, Cancun, Mexico, 2016.

- Y. Chebotar, K. Hausman, **Z. Su**, A. Molchanov, O. Kroemer, G.S. Sukhatme, and S. Schaal, **Bigs: Biotac grasp stability dataset**, in *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA) Workshop on Grasping and Manipulation Datasets*, Stockholm, Sweden, 2016.
- Z. Su, K. Hausman, Y. Chebotar, A. Molchanov, G. Loeb, G. Sukhatme, S. Schaal, Slip Classification Using Tangential and Torsional Skin Distortions on a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor, in *The British Machine Vision Association (BMVA) Workshop on Visual, Tactile and Force Sensing for Robot Manipulation*, 2015
- Z. Su, K. Hausman, Y. Chebotar, A. Molchanov, G. Loeb, G. Sukhatme, S. Schaal, Slip Detection and Classification for Grip Control using Multiple Sensory Modalities on a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor, in *IROS Workshop on Multimodal Sensor-Based Robot Control for HRI and Soft Manipulation*, 2015.
- **Z.** Su, and G. E. Loeb. Haptic robot and human psychophysical studies: A complementary framework to decode haptic perception, in *Biomedical Engineering Society Annual Meeting*, 2014
- **Z.** Su, J. A. Fishel, T. Yamamoto and G. E. Loeb, Use of Tactile Feedback to Control Robotic Palpation to Characterize Object Hardness, in *Biomedical Engineering Society Annual Meeting*, 2012
- **Z.** Su, C. H. Lin, Y. Li and G. E. Loeb, **Spatial Feature Extraction for a Biomimetic Tactile Sensor**, in *Biomedical Engineering Society Annual Meeting*, 2011.

# SCHOLARSHIPS AND AWARDS

- 2015-2018 Max Planck Institute Fellowship (Germany)
- 2014-2015 NSF Body Engineering Fellowship
- 2011-2014 Best Poster Award in USC Fred S. Grodins Research Symposium
  - 09.2007 1st place, Liaoning Province, 7th Chinese National Undergraduate Electronic-Design Contest
- 2004-2007 Shenyang University of Technology Annual Scholarship
- 2004-2007 Outstanding Academic Achievements Award, Shenyang University of Technology
  - 07.2004 Honor for Social Work, Shenyang University of Technology

#### **PROFESSIONAL ACTITIVIES**

#### **Reviewer:**

ICRA 2017-2018, IROS 2016-2017, CoRL 2018, RSS 2017, Robotics and Autonomous Systems, IEEE Transactions on Haptics, IEEE Transactions on Robotics

#### Organizer:

IROS 2018 Workshop: RoboTac: New Progress in Tactile Perception and Learning in Robotics, submitted Humanoids 2016 Workshop: Tactile sensing for manipulation: new progress and challenges

#### **ENTREPRENEURIAL ACTITIVIES**

2014-2015 Our Medical, Inc., Chief Executive Officer and Chief Technology Officer Responsible for team building, product development of an inflatable hip protector

## HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE SKILLS

Programming Languages: C/C++, MATLAB, Python, Assembly, ROS, LaTeX

Operating Systems and Tools: Linux and Xenomai (real-time), Git, programming embedded systems (microprocessors)

Machine Learning: Supervised, unsupervised, reinforcement learning, deep learning (Tensorflow)

**Design:** Solidworks, Mastercam